<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts.atom"/>
  <title>Dynasol Eyewear - Blog</title>
  <updated>2019-10-17T15:12:00-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/about-polarized-sunglasses</id>
    <published>2019-10-17T15:12:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2019-10-17T15:43:52-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/about-polarized-sunglasses"/>
    <title>About Polarized Sunglasses</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-polarized-collection">Polarized sunglasses</a><span> are a great choice for anyone who spends their time outdoors. If you are outside for sports or activities like driving, hiking, fishing, or at the beach, especially where there are lots of glares and reflections, polarized sunglasses will reduce glares and minimize reflections while keeping your eyes protected. Just like going out to the beach you usually put on sunscreen to protect your skin, you will need a pair of sunglasses to protect your eyes...</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/about-polarized-sunglasses">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2><strong>Who wears polarized sunglasses?</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-polarized-collection">Polarized sunglasses</a> are a great choice for anyone who spends their time outdoors. If you are outside for sports or activities like driving, hiking, fishing, or at the beach, especially where there are lots of glares and reflections, polarized sunglasses will reduce glares and minimize reflections while keeping your eyes protected. Just like going out to the beach you usually put on sunscreen to protect your skin, you will need a pair of sunglasses to protect your eyes.</p>
<h2><strong>Benefits of wearing polarized sunglasses</strong></h2>
<ul>
<li>Reduce reflection and glares to improve overall visibility</li>
<li>Enhance contrast and color perception</li>
<li>Reduce eye strain</li>
</ul>
<h2><strong>How to tell if the sunglasses are polarized</strong></h2>
<p>If you are unsure if your sunglasses are polarized:</p>
<h4>Using your computer screen (most computer screens have the same anti-glare technology as polarized sunglasses)</h4>
<p><img alt="Polarized Testing on Computer Screen" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/polarized-testing-computer-screen_1024x1024.jpg?v=1571349371"></p>
<ol>
<li>Open to a white screen, the brightness will be optimal for testing.</li>
<li>Face the sunglasses towards the screen and tilt it 60 to 90 degrees</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<ul>
<li>If the lens becomes dark then the sunglasses are polarized</li>
</ul>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<h4>Using another pair of polarized sunglasses (from our selection of <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-polarized-plastic-sunglasses">wholesale polarized sunglasses</a>)</h4>
<p><img alt="Polarized Sunglasses Testing with another Polarized Sunglasses" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/polarized-testing-another-polarized_1024x1024.jpg?v=1571349471"></p>
<ol>
<li>Place the for sure polarized sunglasses facing down horizontally</li>
<li>Place the sunglasses in question at 90 degrees facing down vertically of the for sure polarized sunglasses (making a +)</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<ul>
<li>If the lens becomes dark then the sunglasses are polarized</li>
</ul>
</ul>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/dynasol-eyewear-delivers-the-best-sunglasses-wholesale-around</id>
    <published>2019-02-11T18:10:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2019-02-11T18:10:39-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/dynasol-eyewear-delivers-the-best-sunglasses-wholesale-around"/>
    <title>Dynasol Eyewear Delivers the Best sunglasses wholesale</title>
    <author>
      <name>Networking Bizz Digital Marketing Collaborator</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>Dynasol Eyewear is offering the largest assortment of the different sunglasses and includes the most advantageous wholesale offers in order to make the purchase as affordable as it is possible. In order to learn a bit more about it, feel free to check out the official webpage. </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/dynasol-eyewear-delivers-the-best-sunglasses-wholesale-around">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/Untitled-1_4dbfbe6e-684d-413b-8540-d819f2d47e22_large.jpg?v=1547162265" alt="sunglasses wholesale"></p>
<p>Dynasol Eyewear is offering the largest assortment of top quality fashion wholesale sunglasses for the very best prices on the market. </p>
<p>Though the summer season is still a bit far from us, there are plenty of places in this world where you will need sunglasses. After all, sunglasses protect your eyes from the direct sunlight that is basically ultraviolet light pointing directly in your eyes and deteriorating them slowly. However, sunglasses are also an accessory – a part of fashion, trend and style. Which is why you may want to benefit from getting the best wholesale fashion sunglasses on the market. </p>
<p>Dynasol Eyewear is there to deliver on just that. With years of experience on the market, the seller figured one thing out – the clients are looking for the ideal combination of both the price and the quality. So the sunglasses wholesale here are available in the largest variety of different styles and trends and, if you are looking for the ideal way to really make the most from the product, its functionality and its looks, then this is exactly the right spot just for you. The sunglasses wholesale are already available and will allow you to benefit from the greatest advantages on the market. You can browse through the existing collections and order the wholesale sunglasses within the very least amount of time possible in order to benefit from the discreet as well as genuinely fast worldwide shipping. There is truly a little something for anyone, regardless of the kind of style and trend you may prefer in the first place. So, if you are looking for the definitive way to really make the most from the sunglasses that look the part, do not hesitate to check out the above-mentioned solution and you will definitely keep on coming back for more.</p>
<p>Unlike many other options out there, these genuinely stylish glasses will not cost you a small fortune and will really look exceptionally great on you all the time. So go ahead, discover the best the market has to offer and you will definitely keep on coming back for much more.</p>
<p>About Dynasol Eyewear:</p>
<p>Dynasol Eyewear is offering the largest assortment of the different sunglasses and includes the most advantageous wholesale offers in order to make the purchase as affordable as it is possible. In order to learn a bit more about it, feel free to check out the official webpage. </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/what-are-some-popular-wholesale-eyewear-styles</id>
    <published>2018-08-13T12:27:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-10T15:35:21-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/what-are-some-popular-wholesale-eyewear-styles"/>
    <title>What are some popular wholesale sunglasses eyewear styles?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><strong></strong>Eyewear can be quiet stylish if you are following the trend. Every year a lot of eyeglasses are launched in the market which are of various styles and can enhance the look of a particular facial structure. Eyewear can be an excellent accessory that reinvents the entire look. Starting from thin frame glasses to thick metal frames or round glasses and the aviator styles, one can easily buy a sunglass that compliments their face. Whether you want to look old school or stylish, it will completely depend on your pick of spectacles.</p>
<p>The trend of eyewear is cyclic as every new style come and go. There are many fashion influencers who love to experiment with their eyewear and this is also a major reason why people do not hesitate to wear glasses nowadays. It can transform the entire look and you will definitely get the right specs from a plethora of options.</p>
<p><strong><br> </strong>At present, eyewear which has a perfect sleeker look or the ones with oversized looks are gaining much popularity. The spectacles with bold colors or the mixed material are also the trend of this season.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Thin frames: </strong>Thin frames made of metal was a favorite in the 90s time. It is also considered to be the hottest eyewear of this year. This eyewear is slimmed down for adding more perfection to the sculpted lines and it can make your face look sleeker and light will fall on your face. If you are very much into wearing the thin glasses then you can easily reinvent your look by opting for metal frames which are inspired by the 70’s look. You can also opt for the frame which is made of thin metal and round in size or the aviator which is large. It is a very playful style and it will never fail to make you look stylish. The thin frames of metal are very much infiltrating in Hollywood as starting from Gigi Hadid to many other models, they just swear on this eyewear for looking fashionable every time.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Retro Minimalism: </strong>Eyewears have gone through a lot of transformation. In earlier days, people used to wear the glasses which are considered to be retro nowadays and you can find that at present that people wear small sized frames. But if you want to add some retro look and make yourself look old school then you can opt for retro eyewear. In the fashion world, retro glasses are famous not only because it is oversized but they are also blended with another type of glasses like aviators and cat eyes to make it look more perfect. Retro glasses are created after incorporating different kind of materials like metal and blending them with the latest style.<strong> </strong>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Wooden: </strong>If you want to wear an eyewear that looks completely natural then you can opt for the eyewear that has the color of the wood. It is a strong emerging trend nowadays as it has a wooden effect on it and sometimes the frame is actually made of wood. In wooden eyeglasses, you can find a different kind of shades starting from olive, wood, sandalwood, khaki, and They will not only compliment your entire outfit but they are also eco- friendly. They are glamorous and delicate and can make you look no less than a celebrity.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Transparent and colorful hues: </strong>This kind of frames is considered to be favorite for a bold look is women love wearing them for a mature look. They look very big and practical and this durable frame is also lightweight so you can also wear it the entire time. You can get the acetate frames in different sizes and shapes so you can easily pick your favorite color that can match-up with the everyday style. There are transparent frames of three kinds of colors like grey, pink, brown which are used with an acetate This will help the woman to get a sophisticated look.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Blue light blocking frame:</strong> Nowadays technology has made people sit in front of them for long hours especially the office goers. So you will need a lens that can easily block these blue lights and protect your vision. The rays which come from the computer will strain your eyes and whenever you will wear this kind of frame the eye health will be healthy for a long time. They are also known as reading glasses or glasses that are used during working on the computer for reducing the eye strain caused by digital device or computer.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>How to style yourself with eyewear</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Looking into the face shape is the very first thing that is required if you want the eyewear to compliment your look.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Depending on your utility you will have to determine whether you want a thick or light frame. Wearing a light frame same will help you to keep it on your eyes without having any marks on the face.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>The color is also very important because you are not going to buy different eyewear for different colors so you will need to take one that will complement every outfit of yours.<strong> </strong>
</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Mixing and matching is the best thing that you can do if you want to look stylish. Starting from cat eye glasses to aviator, you can buy<strong> Wholesale sunglasses. </strong>Sunglasses are also available in the similar shapes and styles.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>Apart from the frame, the lens is as important. Having lenses of a reputed brand will ensure the longevity of the eyewear.</li>
</ul>
<p>This is a guide on what to take this year. This eyewear is trending and will help you to keep yourself updated with the fashion but will also help you to do experiment with your look. Comfort comes first before fashion, so always pick an eyewear which you can carry out otherwise it won't compliment your personality. People who are only dependent on the eyewear for a perfect vision can definitely opt for this kind of frames to enhance their look. There are various places where you can get more varieties of this eyewear as well as<strong> Sunglasses wholesale.</strong></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/your-one-stop-shop-for-wholesale-sunglasses</id>
    <published>2018-07-02T16:27:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:35:20-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/your-one-stop-shop-for-wholesale-sunglasses"/>
    <title>YOUR ONE STOP SHOP FOR WHOLESALE SUNGLASSES!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Welcome to Dynasol Eyewear! For over 10 years, Dynasol Eyewear has provided high-quality wholesale eyewear to the masses. Carrying the latest styles for adults and kids alike, our selection of wholesale fashion sunglasses and readers are always growing. We graciously welcome back all past customers and encourage new customers to see for themselves why Dynasol’s<span> </span><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-new-arrivals">bulk order sunglasses<span> </span></a>and readers are better than the competition.</p>
<p>Completely reasonable in price, but never lacking in quality, you can rest assured that the bulk order sunglasses and readers you receive from Dynasol Eyewear will feel and look great. We have plenty of options available currently and we frequently update our stock with new styles to give you the latest and greatest<span> </span>wholesale eyewear anywhere. We currently have sunglasses available in plastic, metal, or bamboo. We also have a variety of styles including Aviator, Brow Bar, Mirrored, Polarized, Cat Eye, Round, Oversized, and many more. We proudly supply our customers with brands such as BeOne, FROYA, Oxigen, &amp; Pablo Zanetti.</p>
<p>All of our<span> </span><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-fashion-sunglasses">wholesale fashion sunglasses<span> </span></a>and reading glasses are sold by the dozen. When you find the style or styles that you like, simply add the frames to your cart and you will receive that style in the assorted colors as shown. We look forward to working with all of our customers in providing completely fashionable and affordable frames time and time again.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/last-minute-halloween-costume-ideas</id>
    <published>2017-10-25T10:29:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:40:03-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/last-minute-halloween-costume-ideas"/>
    <title>Last Minute Halloween Costume Ideas</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/123_large.png?v=1508952457" alt="Wholesale Aviator Sunglasses" width="516" height="258"></p>
<p>Many people start planning their Halloween costume months in advance, but many people also wait until the last minute. With Halloween right around the corner, we thought we would help you pull together your costume quickly. Sunglasses could set your outfit apart even if you came up with it last minute. Listed below are just three of the many costumes you can wear this Halloween that look great with sunglasses.</p>
<p> <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/7110-n"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_jpg_large.png?v=1508952480" alt="Wholesale Aviator Sunglasses" width="518" height="259"></a></p>
<p><strong>Nerd-</strong> Geek out this Halloween with a nerd costume! To achieve this look you can wear overalls, sneakers, sunglasses, slick hair, long socks, and a bow tie. Our 7110 N sunglasses will make your costume even more convincing.</p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/9090-chrome"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog2_large.png?v=1508952497" alt="Wholesale Aviator Sunglasses" width="512" height="256"></a></p>
<p><strong>Professional Pilot- </strong>Our <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-classic-aviator-sunglasses-metal-mirror-lens-9090-chrome">wholesale aviator sunglasses</a> are ideal for becoming a pilot. With a white t-shirt, dark pants, tie, name tag, and a pair of aviator sunglasses, you will look the part. We suggest our 9090 Chrome sunglasses. This iconic look will surely win over the crowd.</p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/7110-black-sd"><strong><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/Capture_large.PNG?v=1508952511" alt="Wholesale Aviator Sunglasses" width="524" height="262"></strong></a></p>
<p><strong>Rock Star- </strong>Are you ready to rock and roll all night long? If so, a rock star might just be the perfect Halloween costume for you. You could wear a dark shirt, leather jacket or vest, fingerless gloves, stick on tattoos, and a guitar. Do not forget the rock star outfit is not complete without a pair of sunglasses. We suggest our 7110 black SD sunglasses.</p>
<p>Whether you are going trick-or-treating or passing out candy to the children in your neighborhood, you should still have a creative costume. If your outfit could benefit from sunglasses, you can count on Dynasol Eyewear to have the pair you need. Start shopping our sunglasses to bring your costume to the next level.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/uv-protection</id>
    <published>2017-10-25T10:26:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:40:25-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/uv-protection"/>
    <title>UV Protection</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_04d1bed9-6599-4a9a-9442-fb8b297376fe_large.jpg?v=1508952320" alt="Wholesale Sunglasses" style="float: right;"></p>
<p>When you walk outside, it is almost second nature to put sunglasses on your face because of the brightness. However, there is another reason to wear sunglasses and that is to protect the health of your eyes. People wear sunscreen to protect themselves from the UV rays, so it makes sense to wear sunglasses to shield your eyes.</p>
<p><strong>UVA Rays- </strong>This particular type of ray has longer wavelengths, which allow the beams to go through glass. The back of your eye is at risk when it comes to UVA rays because it can damage your macula and affect your central vision.</p>
<p><strong>UVB Rays- </strong>Although all UV rays can be harmful to your eyes and skin, UVB rays are very dangerous. UVB rays can damage your cornea because the front of your eye absorbs the majority of this ray. You could develop certain types of cataracts over time from the damage.</p>
<p><strong>UV 400-</strong> This type of protection can shield your eyes from both UVA and UVB rays. UV 400 can block up to 99% of both of these rays. All of our <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/froya-french-collection-wholesale-sunglasses">wholesale sunglasses</a> have UV 400 protection, so you can be sure your eyes are protected from the sun’s glare when you are outside.</p>
<p>Now that you are aware of the dangers UV rays pose to your eyes, you should wear sunglasses whenever you are outside, even if it is cloudy because the UV rays can go through the clouds. Your eyes are important to us, which is why we only sell wholesale sunglasses with UV 400 protection. Start shopping our selection today.</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/fall-sunglasses-trends-for-2017-part-two</id>
    <published>2017-09-22T11:01:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:42:26-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/fall-sunglasses-trends-for-2017-part-two"/>
    <title>Fall Sunglasses Trends for 2017 Part Two</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>In our previous post, we discussed top trends for fall! Of course, we couldn’t fit all the trends in one post, so we are going to continue the list of trendy sunglasses you must have for fall. When it comes to keeping up with the latest trends, you can always count on <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/froya-french-collection-wholesale-sunglasses">FROYA collection of sunglasses</a>.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_60ba4377-6ecc-4c4f-bab2-09194cfc4fe3_large.jpg?v=1506103265" alt="FROYA Collection Sunglasses"></p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-sunglasses-round-retro-chunky-fc-6353">Round</a>- These round sunglasses (FC 6353) are a part of the FROYA collection and are only $34.00 per dozen. When you purchase these sunglasses by the dozen, you will receive an assortment of colors. What better way to kick off fall than by wearing these sunglasses with a brow bar?</p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_png_4b92e675-e704-470b-a34d-073357711a7a_large.jpg?v=1506103285" alt="FROYA Collection Sunglasses"></p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-sunglasses-classic-women-cat-eye-fc-6359">Cat Eye</a>- This particular pair of cat eye sunglasses are FC 6359 and can be purchased for $35.00 per dozen. When you choose the darker frames, you are complementing your outfit without a pop of color. Neutral tones and deeper color shades are in for fall because it matches with the season. You can decide which gorgeous color you want to wear when you purchase these sunglasses by the dozen.</p>
<p>If you love the FROYA collection of sunglasses, you will definitely want to purchase these two styles for fall. If you have any questions, contact us today at (626) 444-6181 for assistance.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/fall-sunglasses-trends-for-2017-part-one</id>
    <published>2017-09-22T10:58:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:39:12-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/fall-sunglasses-trends-for-2017-part-one"/>
    <title>Fall Sunglasses Trends for 2017 Part One</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>When you think of fall, you naturally think of pumpkins and colorful leaves. Sunglasses are not the first thing to come to mind, but that does not mean you shouldn’t protect your eyes from harmful rays. We compiled a list of our top styles for the upcoming season. If you want to purchase sunglasses at wholesale price, take a look at our list of top fall sunglasses below.</p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_258d746a-a0fa-4fce-ae75-0d7753c000c0_large.jpg?v=1506103072" alt="Sunglasses Wholesale"></p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-fashion-sunglasses-horn-rimmed">Classic</a>- Let your style shine through this fall with the 7110 Tortoise Matte wholesale fashion sunglasses. You can purchase this color by the dozen for only $14.00. Neutral colors are always in during fall because the rich colors coordinate with many outfits. These glasses will look fantastic with whichever color you are wearing on a particular day.</p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_png_c1215103-92f1-431b-8b9a-1c96a262be97_large.jpg?v=1506103092" alt="Sunglasses Wholesale"></p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-aviator-sunglasses">Aviator</a>- Fall is all about the basics, so it makes sense that the classic aviator sunglasses are a go-to accessory to complement your fall outfit. This classic look can be worn throughout the seasons because it is versatile. If you are interested in purchasing this pair, the style number is 2314 and the price is $30.00 per dozen.</p>
<p>Get ready for fall by buying <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-fashion-sunglasses">sunglasses at wholesale</a> prices. Give us a call at (626) 444-6181 if you have any questions when placing an order.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/finding-your-face-shape</id>
    <published>2017-08-10T10:08:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:44:42-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/finding-your-face-shape"/>
    <title>Finding Your Face Shape</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_6cb36fc9-02fd-4589-963b-2fe1d71148bf_large.jpg?v=1502384817" alt="Wholesale Sunglasses" style="float: right;">Determining the shape of your face can be a challenge, but we want to make it easier than ever. Follow our guide below and you will be able to distinctly identify your face shape.</p>
<p><strong>Round-</strong>If you do not have any hard lines on your face and your face is almost circular, then you most likely have a round-shaped face. It is common for the forehead and jawline to be the same width.</p>
<p><strong>Oval- </strong>This face shape is very similar to round, but the forehead is normally wider than the chin. Unlike the round-shaped face, your jawline has a slight curve to it.  </p>
<p><strong>Heart-</strong> If you have a heart-shaped face, then you have a wider forehead and a pointed jawline that leads to your chin. The chin is your smallest part of your face. </p>
<p><strong>Square- </strong>When you have a square face, your chin is flat or shaped like a square. People with square faces often have a very strong jawline.</p>
<p>Now that you know your face shape, you can discover the ideal pair of <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-usa-flag">wholesale sunglasses</a> to compliment your face. If you have a square or oval face shape, click <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/wholesale-sunglasses-to-fit-your-face-part-1">here</a>. If you have a heart or round face shape, click <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/wholesale-sunglasses-to-fit-your-face-part-2">here</a>. Shop our different styles of sunglasses before having fun in the sun.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/wholesale-sunglasses-to-fit-your-face-part-2</id>
    <published>2017-08-10T10:08:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:38:25-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/wholesale-sunglasses-to-fit-your-face-part-2"/>
    <title>Wholesale Sunglasses to Fit Your Face Part 2</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>In a previous post, we talk about which frames match your face shape best. In that post, we described the ideal <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-cat-eye-sunglasses">wholesale sunglasses</a> for square and oval faces. If you have one of those face shapes you can check it out <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/wholesale-sunglasses-to-fit-your-face-part-1">here</a>. Feel great and look even better by picking the right shades to match your face shape. Keep reading if you have a heart or round face. If you are unsure what your face shape is, take a look at our post Finding Your Face Shape <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/finding-your-face-shape">here</a>.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_large.jpg?v=1502384659" alt="Wholesale Sunglasses"></p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-womens-sunglasses-cat-eye-8523">Heart</a>- If you have a heart-shaped face, then you should try wearing cat eye sunglasses. The pointed ends of the frames will compliment your strong jawline and accentuate the smallest part of your face which is your chin. This particular pair of cat eye sunglasses (8523) is only $28 for a dozen in assorted colors. For a meow-nificant summer, purchase the pur-fect pair of cat eye sunglasses.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_6b7bafe5-c3a0-40a3-bb17-a34a1802232f_large.jpg?v=1502384711" alt="Wholesale Sunglasses"></p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-sunglasses-classic-horn-rimmed-super-dark-lens-plastic-7111-sd">Round</a>- Classic sunglasses have rounded lines which will compliment people who have a round face shape. These types of sunglasses will help to elongate your face. You can order multiple wholesale classic sunglasses (7111 SD) by the dozen for only $14.</p>
<p>Here at Dynasol Eyewear, we want you to select your perfect pair of sunglasses! <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/pages/contact-us">Contact us</a> today if you have any questions about the ordering process or about a certain pair of sunglasses.</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/trendy-sunglasses-for-summer-2017</id>
    <published>2017-07-24T08:00:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:46:03-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/trendy-sunglasses-for-summer-2017"/>
    <title>Trendy Sunglasses for Summer 2017</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Warm weather means it is time to wear your favorite sunglasses! Shield your eyes from the sun in style with the latest summer sunglass trends for 2017. We thought we would share the hottest wholesale fashion sunglasses with you before summer is over. There is still time to grab a pair to show off your creative side.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_png_e0d4daa7-e4f9-454f-b307-ef94032eaf63_large.jpg?v=1500307838" alt="Wholesale Fashion Sunglasses"></p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-clear-sunglasses-personality">Clear Lens</a>- Let your personality shine through when you wear sunglasses with clear lens. Even though these glasses have clear lens, they still have UV 400 protection. This bold fashion statement is sure to be the highlight of this summer. You won’t want to be the only one without clear shades. With a variety of frames to choose from you can discover the one that will properly express your personal style.</p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_large.png?v=1500307874" alt="Wholesale Fashion Sunglasses"></p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-sunglasses-metal-horn-rimmed-ocean-flat-lens-8558-col">Color Lens</a>- Add some color to your summer with our fashion sunglasses that feature colorful lens. No matter what outfit you are wearing, your color lens will surely spice it up. Whether your favorite color is blue, green, pink, or red, we have sunglasses to match your style.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_532535fc-ec44-46a2-b9e4-38a4f76e0c96_large.png?v=1500307900" alt="Wholesale Fashion Sunglasses"></p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-cat-eye-sunglasses">Cat Eyes</a>- Tip your summer in the right direction when you wear your cat eye sunglasses. With a fierce look like this, you are sure to have a fun-filled summer to remember. This particular pair of cat eye sunglasses (FC 6351) is available in an assortment of colors including black, beige, demi, tortoise, and navy blue.</p>
<p>Kick off your summer with <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-polarized-collection">wholesale fashion sunglasses</a> from Dynasol Eyewear. View this summer through different color lens or even clear lens by shopping our selection today.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/wholesale-sunglasses-to-fit-your-face-part-1</id>
    <published>2017-07-17T09:13:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:43:40-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/wholesale-sunglasses-to-fit-your-face-part-1"/>
    <title>Wholesale Sunglasses to Fit Your Face Part 1</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Embrace this summer by wearing the right pair of <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-cat-eye-sunglasses">wholesale sunglasses</a> to frame your face. Depending on the shape of your face, certain sunglasses will look better on you. Dynasol Eyewear wants you to look your best whenever you go outside, so we have provided a list of sunglass styles to match your face shape.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_png_large.jpg?v=1500307692" alt="Wholesale Sunglasses"></p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-sunglasses-aviator-brow-bar-fc-6000">Square</a>- Aviators look the best if you have a square face because this type of frame can soften a strong jawline while still looking stylish. Are you ready for a life-changing summer? If you have a square face and haven’t tried wearing aviators, it’s time to branch out.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_png_1dd5d283-19ce-469e-af4f-f1f1ca1d0f19_large.jpg?v=1500307727" alt="Wholesale Sunglasses"></p>
<p><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/oversized-wholesale-sunglasses-with-flat-top-and-flat-lens-7964">Oval-</a> Not many face shapes can pull off oversized sunglasses, but people with oval faces definitely can. Don’t be afraid to step out of your comfort zone and try something new. Be bold this summer and pick out a pair of oversized sunglasses.</p>
<p>We hope this guideline helps you purchase the perfect pair of shades this summer. If you have a heart or round face shape, click <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/wholesale-sunglasses-to-fit-your-face-part-2">here</a>. Style is all about personal expression, so you can never go wrong with wholesale sunglasses you love. If your face shape doesn’t line up with the frames you love, it’s okay to embrace your own style. Discover sunglasses you’ll love when you shop with us.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/3-benefits-of-bulk-ordering-sunglasses</id>
    <published>2017-07-14T08:00:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:47:18-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/3-benefits-of-bulk-ordering-sunglasses"/>
    <title>3 Benefits of Bulk Ordering Sunglasses</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_png_bb6f410e-5ee6-40c6-a9a1-e4b7c03cb420_large.jpg?v=1500308270" alt="Bulk Order Sunglasses" style="float: right;">Whether you are purchasing a <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/restocked-wholesale-sunglasses">bulk order of sunglasses</a> for your business or as party favors, you will save time and money by shopping with us. Dynasol Eyewear makes it easy and convenient for you to find the style and color you are looking for.  Here are just a few of the many benefits of buying in bulk with us.</p>
<p><strong>Save Money-</strong> The more you buy, the more you save. When you purchase in bulk, you are saving money compared to purchasing each pair individually. Get more for your money when you purchase sunglasses with us.</p>
<p><strong>Wide Selection-</strong> Our wide array of sunglasses will give you multiple choices, but it gets even better. Once you select a pair of glasses, we send you the same pair of sunglasses in assorted colors. You have a variety of styles to choose from and then you will receive an assortment of colors of your chosen style. The possibilities are endless.</p>
<p><strong>Convenience-</strong> You don’t have to worry about finding popular sunglasses in different colors because we send you a variety. All you have to do is select the style of glasses you like and we will do the rest. We make shopping with us easy.</p>
<p>Next time you are thinking about purchasing sunglasses, remember to bulk order sunglasses with Dynasol Eyewear. <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-mirrored-lens">Shop</a> our mirrored lens section today!</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/3-ways-wholesale-sunglasses-can-protect-your-eyes-this-summer</id>
    <published>2017-07-07T05:08:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:46:48-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/3-ways-wholesale-sunglasses-can-protect-your-eyes-this-summer"/>
    <title>3 Ways Wholesale Sunglasses can Protect Your Eyes this Summer</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/blog_png_5f6fe517-acb2-4ac0-94d9-0e888d1ada1d_large.jpg?v=1500308358" alt="Wholesale Sunglasses" style="float: right;">Protect your eyes from the sun this summer with <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-with-flat-lens">wholesale sunglasses</a>. Many people think sunglasses are just a fashion accessory, but they do have another purpose such as protecting your eyes. Your eyes will thank you for shielding them from the sun and other debris. Here are just a few benefits of wearing eye protection this summer.</p>
<p><strong>Yard Work-</strong> Sunglasses can prevent dirt, grass, and other tiny debris from making its way into your eyes while you are doing yard work. Whether you are mowing the lawn or planting a new flower, keep your sunglasses on to prevent anything from scratching your eyes. Plus, you are fashionable while working in the yard.</p>
<p><strong>UV Rays-</strong> Anytime you go outside, your eyes are subjected to the sun’s powerful UV rays. Extended exposure may lead to cataracts down the road. Keep your eyes healthy by protecting them from the bright sunlight and UV rays. Your vision is important, so put sunglasses on when you walk outside.</p>
<p><strong>Safety-</strong> When driving the sun’s glare can be too bright for you to drive safely. The sun visor doesn’t always block the brightness depending on the time of day. Sunglasses prevent the brightness from reaching your eyes, allowing you to drive safely.</p>
<p>When you are looking for fashionable eye protection, you can count on Dynasol Eyewear to have every style of wholesale sunglasses you need. <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-new-arrivals">Browse</a> our assortment of sunglasses today.   </p>
<br>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/sunglasses-styles-for-trips-to-the-beach</id>
    <published>2017-05-19T10:45:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:47:58-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/sunglasses-styles-for-trips-to-the-beach"/>
    <title>Sunglasses Styles for Trips to the Beach</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="wholesale oversized sunglasses" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/DSC_5563_medium.jpg?v=1496425506" style="float: right;"><br>
<p>With warmer weather moving in across the country, many people already have summer vacation on their brain. Summer vacation for a lot of people, means a nice beach getaway. If you plan on going to the beach this year, you need the right pair of sunglasses to go with your summer wardrobe. For some people, multiple pairs of sunglasses will be required. Here are a few things to consider when choosing the right pair of sunglasses for your beach vacation:</p>
<p><strong>UV Protection</strong> – The most important thing about selecting sunglasses for the beach is the need for UV protection. If not efficiently protected, your eyes can withstand a lot of damage from the harmful UV rays of the sun. It is for this reason that you will want sunglasses that will provide adequate UV protection. Dynasol Eyewear carries wholesale sunglasses with 100% UV protection, so you can protect your eyes at the beach and look great while doing it.</p>
<p><strong>Big Lenses</strong> – Not only will bigger lenses provide more protection from the sun, they will look incredibly fashionable. The oversized glasses trend is always in style and they look even better when you wear them on the beach. We carry a wide variety of <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-oversized-sunglasses">wholesale oversized sunglasses</a> to go with your whole summer wardrobe.</p>
<p>If you want the <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-sunglasses-large-plastic-round-color-mirror-lens-8546">8546 style</a> or other wholesale oversized sunglasses for your beach trip this summer, you need to place a bulk order with Dynasol Eyewear today.<span style="text-decoration: line-through;"></span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/pairing-your-facial-hair-with-sunglasses</id>
    <published>2017-05-12T10:42:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:48:43-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/pairing-your-facial-hair-with-sunglasses"/>
    <title>Pairing Your Facial Hair with Sunglasses</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="wholesale eyewear" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/may1_medium.jpg?v=1496425312" style="float: right;"><br>
<p>The beard is integral to the fashion mix. Much like choosing a hairstyle or hat, growing and styling facial hair dramatically affects your appearance. As with sunglasses, the choice for facial hair styling is influenced by culture and trends, personal style, and face shape. Whether you have a full beard or just a mustache, pairing facial hair with your favorite styles of <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-deals">wholesale eyewear</a> can be tricky. Keep reading to learn what pairings we recommend.</p>
<p><strong>Beard</strong></p>
<p>The medium-length, standard beard gives your face a slightly more oval, elongated look. Complement this with angular frames that are also wide enough to compensate for the added length given to the face. To complement a full beard, go with thinner framed glasses, like aviators. These are stylish, but won’t draw as much attention as a thicker frame.</p>
<p><strong>Stubble</strong><br> More square, angular frames will add definition to your face. If you have stubble, go with a thicker classic shape to match the look.</p>
<p><strong>Mustache</strong></p>
<p>The classic mustache works best with glasses that align with your browline, and have a thicker frame on top. For a fuller mustache, try a pair of round frames or aviators.</p>
<p><strong>Goatee</strong></p>
<p>Because goatees can make your chin look bigger and ounder, rectangular aviators are the best complement for the style.</p>
<p>Order our <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-aviator-sunglasses-metal-brow-bar-2303">2303 Aviator sunglasses</a> and many other great wholesale sunglasses online.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/how-to-encourage-your-kids-to-wear-sunglasses</id>
    <published>2017-04-28T11:59:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:50:03-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/how-to-encourage-your-kids-to-wear-sunglasses"/>
    <title>How to Encourage Your Kids to Wear Sunglasses</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="4567-7 kids plastic sunglasses with color mirror lenses" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/april2_medium.jpg?v=1496170744" style="float: right;"><br>
<p>In our last post we discussed why sunglasses are a crucial part of any kid’s sun protection plan. In order to prevent issues with their eyes, and keep them comfortable in the sun, you should always encourage your kids to wear sunglasses. The problem comes when you try to get your kids to do something new. They may not understand why it’s important, so here are some tips to encourage them to put the glasses on when they go outside:</p>
<p><strong>Be a Role Model</strong></p>
<p>Being a good role model for your kids is the goal of any parent. When your kids see you putting on your sunglasses every time you go outside in sunny weather, they will want to imitate you. Kids look up to their parents and try to emulate them, so do your best to model good sun protection habits for them.</p>
<p><strong>Make Them Cool</strong></p>
<p>Kids want to look cool, so if they think that cool people wear sunglasses, they will be more likely to wear their sunglasses. Show them pictures of their celebrity heroes wearing sunglasses and point out how cool they look wearing them.</p>
<p>It also helps to tell your kids how cool they look when they do put on their sunglasses to reinforce the good behavior.</p>
<p><strong>Let them Choose</strong></p>
<p>Letting your kids pick out their own sunglasses will make the experience more fun for them – and they get to express their own personal style. The <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-kids-sunglasses-classic-horn-rimmed-matte-transparent-frame-color-temple-4567-7">4567-7 collection</a> of kids’ sunglasses from Dynasol comes in a variety of fun band colors and colored mirror lenses. When you need <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-for-kids">wholesale sunglasses</a> for kids, visit DynasolEyewear.com for a wide selection of fun styles to choose from.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/make-sure-your-kids-are-wearing-sunglasses-this-summer</id>
    <published>2017-04-14T11:57:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:50:54-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/make-sure-your-kids-are-wearing-sunglasses-this-summer"/>
    <title>Make Sure Your Kids are Wearing Sunglasses This Summer</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="4567-9 kids plastic sunglasses in orange, rainbow, and purple" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/april1_medium.jpg?v=1496170636" style="float: right;"><br>
<p>Now that summer is right around the corner, it’s time to stock up on sun protection for your kids. Chances are good that your cabinets are already well stocked with kids’ sunscreen, and you’ve probably purchased sun hats for the beach or pool if your children are particularly susceptible to sunburn – but have you thought about sunglasses?</p>
<p><strong>Why Kids Should Wear Sunglasses Outside </strong></p>
<p>You don’t see children with sunglasses on very often, even though adults are constantly wearing them to drive or when out and about. You should be encouraging your kids to wear sunglasses every time they go outside in bright light. UV rays can sunburn their skin, but it can also cause damage to their eyes as well.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Their eyes can get sunburned – </strong>Exposure to UV rays can cause ‘photokeratitis’ or sunburn of the eye. It can also be referred to as snow blindness. This can lead to temporary or sometimes permanent vision loss.</li>
<li>
<strong>Greater risk of eye diseases/Infections – </strong>Too much exposure to sun can put your kids at greater risk for things like cataracts, age-related macular degeneration, and an infection called “surfer’s eye” – a non-cancerous itchy growth on the eye.</li>
<li>
<strong>Cancer – </strong>We have all heard that UV rays can lead to skin cancer, but you are also at risk of developing cancer of the eye or eyelid if sunglasses are not consistently worn.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>4567-9 Kids’ Sunglasses Collection</strong></p>
<p>The <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-kids-sunglasses-classic-horn-rimmed-printed-color-stripes-4567-9">4567-9 collection</a> of kids’ sunglasses are available in a variety of fun colors that your kids will love. Find these and more <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-for-kids">wholesale kids sunglasses</a> today at DynasolEyewear.com.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/reasons-to-buy-a-pair-of-bamboo-reading-glasses</id>
    <published>2017-03-24T05:10:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:52:23-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/reasons-to-buy-a-pair-of-bamboo-reading-glasses"/>
    <title>Reasons to Buy a Pair of Bamboo Reading Glasses</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="wholesale bamboo reading glasses" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/RS_1137_medium.jpg?v=1491307835" style="float: right;"><br>
<p>Too much reading, working on a computer and poor lighting can all create stress on your eyes, but a pair of <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-bamboo-reading-glasses">bamboo reading glasses</a> is an affordable and wise solution to your blurred vision. Reading glasses are a great way to take the stress off of your eyes and regain that clear vision you once had.</p>
<p>Reading glasses don’t require a prescription and they don’t entail the time and financial investment of a visit to the eye doctor. These glasses simply offer magnification on different levels ranging from 1.25 to 4.00. You can try a few different magnifications and see what works best for you. Once you know the level you want, then all you need to do is select the style that best suits your look. Check out the latest styles of wholesale bamboo reading glasses and discover all of the benefits of bamboo frames.</p>
<p>Not only are bamboo frames will be comfortable and long lasting, bamboo products are also very eco-friendly. Unlike other types of wood, bamboo is highly sustainable and the plant is not killed when wood is harvested. This makes bamboo reading glasses an environmentally responsible choice and Dynasol Eyewear has several different styles to choose from for both men and women.  </p>
<p>With Dynasol Eyewear’s bamboo frames, you will look great and your vision will be clear and stress free. Dynasol’s <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-reading-glasses-classic-horn-rimmed-with-bamboo-temple-plastic-rs-1137">RS 1137</a> is a great style currently available from our bamboo reading glasses collection. Browse the rest of our selection and order on our website today.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/did-you-know-that-you-can-sunburn-your-eyes</id>
    <published>2017-03-10T05:08:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:36:25-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/did-you-know-that-you-can-sunburn-your-eyes"/>
    <title>Did You Know That You Can Sunburn Your Eyes?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="wholesale polarized sunglasses – PL 702" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/PL_702_-_3_medium.jpg?v=1491307719" style="float: right;"><br>
<p>Everyone understands that UV rays from the sun can damage their skin, so they wear sunscreen. But did you realize that those same UV rays can damage your eyes? The only way to combat harmful UV rays is to wear sunglasses. There are many conditions that are caused by exposure to UV rays, but protecting your vision is easy to do thanks to the <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-new-arrivals">wholesale sunglasses</a> from Dynasol Eyewear.</p>
<p>Even just short term exposure to UV rays, can cause macular degeneration which is the leading cause of age-related blindness. It also increases your risk of having cataracts, which clouds the lens of your eye and results in cloudy vision. You can even sunburn your cornea, a condition known as photokeratitis.</p>
<p>No one is immune to the damage that UV sun rays can cause. Small children should wear eye protection as the damage will only get worse the longer your eyes are unprotected. It is also important to remember that some medications will increase the eyes’ sensitivity to light so sunglasses are required even under low-light conditions.</p>
<p>Quality sunglasses at an affordable price mean that you can buy several pairs. Our <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-sunglasses-classic-horn-rimmed-polarized-lens-pl-702">PL 702</a> is a great polarized classic style that will go with most wardrobes. Select multiple styles to match your wardrobe and pairs that are designed for different outdoor activities. There are hundreds of styles to choose from like wholesale kids’ sunglasses and readers. Protecting your vision is important, but it doesn’t have to be expensive. Just pick the dozen of sunglasses you like and have them shipped right to you today.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/choosing-the-right-frames</id>
    <published>2017-02-17T12:50:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:53:49-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/choosing-the-right-frames"/>
    <title>Choosing the Right Frames</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>It can be a challenge to find a new pair of sunglasses or reading glasses. Whether you are shopping at a small neighborhood shop or buying from a <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-with-rhinestones">wholesale eyewear</a> provider, there often seems to be too many choices. Using the following tips can make it easier to make purchasing decisions:</p>
<p><strong>Face Shape Considerations</strong></p>
<p>The shape of your face can help you determine the sunglasses or reading glasses that will look best for your face:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Round Face:</strong>Square or rectangular styles tend to be wider than round faces and this helps to slim the appearance of the face.</li>
<li>
<strong>Oval Face:</strong>The best choices are frames that are wider than the broadest area on the face and frames that are geometric in shape.</li>
<li>
<strong>Square Face:</strong>Sunglasses with an oval or round shape can help soften the lines and profile of a squared face shape.</li>
<li>
<strong>Diamond Face:</strong>This type of face is a bit of a challenge to find frames for, but good options are cat eye glasses and oval frames.</li>
<li>
<strong>Heart-Shaped Face:</strong>Frames which focus attention away from the forehead and toward the cheek bones and nose often look the best.  Cat eye sunglasses, round, aviator and other flashy styles would work best.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Skin Tone</strong></p>
<p>More important than hair color or eye color, skin tone impacts the way the frames look and also can change the appearance of your face. Make sure the frames accent your skin tone and consider how they will look in indoor and outdoor light.</p>
<p><strong>What's Your Lifestyle?</strong></p>
<p>There are wholesale sunglasses and reading glasses for every way of life! Do you work outside or play sports? Then you need durable break-proof glasses.  If you are in an office environment, a pair of sleek professional looking frames may be best. Do you need something simple and easy? Then plastic frames might work best for your needs.  Think about the places you go and the things you do each day and use that to help you choose frames that fit your lifestyle.</p>
<p><strong>Your Personality</strong></p>
<p>Are you fun and adventurous? Are you serious and professional? Are you casual and simple? Are you someone always on the go or more of a home-body? Choosing your frames creates a sense of identity that will help to showcase your personality.</p>
<p>If you need affordable, fashionable wholesale eyewear, Dynasol Eyewear has a great selection to choose from, such as our <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-sunglasses-flared-vintage-cat-eye-women-fc-6406">style FC 6406 cat eye sunglasses</a>. Contact us today for more information regarding our wholesale sunglasses and reading glasses.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/the-pros-of-bamboo-frames</id>
    <published>2017-02-10T12:45:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:54:25-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/the-pros-of-bamboo-frames"/>
    <title>The Pros of Bamboo Frames</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="bamboo reading glasses" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/RS_1135_medium.jpg?v=1488487452" style="float: right;"><br>
<p>If you are looking for wholesale reading glasses or wholesale sunglasses, there are many choices that are available. If you want something attractive, cool, and comfortable then you need to consider <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-bamboo-reading-glasses">bamboo reading glasses</a> and sunglasses! These amazing frames are unique and they are becoming very popular among many age groups. When you opt to go with bamboo for your wholesale sunglasses and reading glasses you can enjoy several great benefits:</p>
<p><strong>No Discoloration</strong></p>
<p>Bamboo will not wear as quickly as many other options and it also will not discolor due to exposure to sweat and salt from the body, the sun and other environmental elements. They will last longer and look great unlike other traditional frames.</p>
<p><strong>Light Weight</strong></p>
<p>Bamboo is very light yet surprisingly durable, making them great for reading glasses and sunglasses that get a lot of frequent and long term use. They are light so there is less chance of imprints being made on your face and less pain on your ears and nose when they are worn for long periods of time.</p>
<p><strong>Environmentally Sound</strong></p>
<p>Bamboo is fairly plentiful and much of the bamboo that is used in commercial productions are grown specifically for that purpose leaving wild strands of bamboo untouched. As a material it is a very eco-friendly choice.</p>
<p>Bamboo sunglasses and reading glasses are growing in popularity. You will want to keep these in stock as they will fly off the shelves. Check out our full line of great frames currently available at Dynasol Eyewear today including the <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-reading-glasses-rectangular-horn-rimmed-with-bamboo-temple-plastic-rs-1135">RS 1135</a> bamboo reading glasses. Contact us today with questions regarding products and placing an order.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/ways-to-market-sunglasses</id>
    <published>2017-01-27T05:28:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:55:02-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/ways-to-market-sunglasses"/>
    <title>Ways to Market Sunglasses</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="wholesale reading glasses" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/jan2_medium.jpg?v=1486580783" style="float: right;"><br><br>
<p>Eyewear and sunglasses are a versatile product because they are used for health and safety purposes, certain job occupations, and more importantly, fashion. Since they are versatile in their uses, there are many ways to market them. Here are a few things to consider when marketing your sunglasses and reading glasses.</p>
<p><strong>Display</strong></p>
<p>The most important thing to remember with marketing any type of sunglasses or eyewear is how you display them. If you make your products look trendy and cool, your customers will want to wear them. Another great way to market your sunglasses and eyewear is to have pictures of models and mannequins wearing them around your store. This will allow customers to get a better picture of how they would look in the same pair.</p>
<p><strong>Protection</strong></p>
<p>With the rise in awareness of how dangerous the sun is for the body and eyes, many people gravitate towards sunglasses for health reasons. When marketing your sunglasses, you can promote how the lenses can protect eyes from being damaged by the sun. Polarized sunglasses are growing in popularity. Their ability to block the glare from light and reduce eye fatigue makes them perfect for people looking to seek health benefits from wearing sunglasses.</p>
<p><strong>Location </strong></p>
<p>If you have a storefront, the location is a huge factor in how you will market your sunglasses. For example, if you are choosing to sell your products in a beach town or any place near water, you will want to focus on how they are protective against the sun, durable in the sand, etc. If you choose a city or town and would like to have a high end store, you will want to focus on how trendy and fashionable your sunglasses are.</p>
<p><strong>Focus on a Target Audience</strong></p>
<p>Your customers are the most important part of your business and therefore, you want to attend to their needs and desires first. Many sunglass companies market their products to a specific audience. For example, you can sell wholesale sunglasses that are best for military pilots, outdoor sports fans, motorcyclists, etc.</p>
<p>Once you have decided the purpose of your business, purchasing wholesale sunglasses will help you have enough supply to meet your customers’ demands. If you need high quality, stylish wholesale fashion sunglasses and other sunglasses, trust in the experts at Dynasol Eyewear! For any assistance with ordering our <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-reading-glasses">wholesale eyewear</a><span>,</span> including wholesale sunglasses and wholesale reading glasses like our <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-reading-glasses-classic-horn-rimmed-cat-eye-plastic-rs-1024">RS 1024</a> reading glasses, please give us a call today at (626) 444-6181.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/tips-for-starting-an-eyewear-business</id>
    <published>2017-01-20T05:26:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:56:13-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/tips-for-starting-an-eyewear-business"/>
    <title>Tips For Starting an Eyewear Business</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>The eyewear business is one of the best industries to go into because of how in demand the products are and the numerous options you have for your business. To learn more about starting your own eyewear business, please read on!</p>
<p><strong>Foundation of Your Business</strong></p>
<p>The first step to starting any business is to determine how you want to market your product. Some great starting points:</p>
<ul>
<li>The story of how and why you started the business</li>
<li>Promote any unique or special materials- wood, horn, bamboo, carbon, etc.</li>
<li>Focus on lifestyle- vibrant colors, fun designs, street smart, casual, high fashion, etc.</li>
</ul>
<ul></ul>
<p><strong>Research</strong></p>
<p>Once you’ve decided how you want to market your business, you will want to do extensive research to find out the best place to sell your products, what your customers like, how much inventory you should buy to start, seasonality, etc.</p>
<p><strong>Location</strong></p>
<p>If you are selling from a physical storefront, the location should also be chosen based on how you want to market your products. For example, if you’re choosing to sell funky, unique sunglasses, you can find a touristy spot in a beach town. However, if you want to sell high fashion and trendy sunglasses, you might want to find a location in a city or town.  </p>
<p>Our <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-sunglasses-cat-eye-women-classic-fc-6365">FC 6365</a>  wholesale cat eye sunglasses are just one of many fabulous styles we have to offer. If you are starting your own sunglass company and are in need of high quality, trendy wholesale sunglasses and wholesale reading glasses, trust in Dynasol Eyewear! We carry only the latest styles for men, women, and children.</p>
<p>For help with ordering any of our <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/styles">wholesale fashion sunglasses</a>, please give us a call at (626) 444-6181.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/winter-2017-sunglass-trends-oversized-sunglasses</id>
    <published>2017-01-13T13:01:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:56:43-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/winter-2017-sunglass-trends-oversized-sunglasses"/>
    <title>Winter 2017 Sunglass Trends: Oversized Sunglasses</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p style="float: right;"><a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/styles"><img alt="Froya FC 6289" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/FC6289-6_medium.jpg?v=1485464522" style="float: right;"></a>Are you interested in staying on trend? Every season of every year brings fashion and style trends that everyone must have. The winter of 2017 is no different. There are specific trends for sunglasses right now that you will absolutely want to get in on if you want to be stylish and fashionable. Dynasol Eyewear is a <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-fashion-sunglasses">sunglasses distributor</a> that prides itself in having the latest high-quality, fashionable, yet affordable sunglasses.<br><br>So you want to be in trend for winter 2017? This winter, one style that is incredibly popular is the oversized sunglasses. Oversized sunglasses have made appearances in the United States and popular culture since the 1960s. Former first lady, Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis, better known as “Jackie O” was often spotted wearing oversized sunglasses. Oversized sunglasses have also been seen on Elton John in the 70s and became very popular in the 1980s. Fashion experts claim that in 2017, the oversized sunglasses aren’t going anywhere. On the runways, in TV and movies, and the everyday lives of the rich and fabulous, oversized sunglasses can be seen in a variety of shapes, colors and styles.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;">Follow this great trend by supplying your area with fashionable, high-quality oversized sunglasses like the <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/products/wholesale-sunglasses-women-oversize-butterfly-fc-6289">Froya FC 6289</a> pictured above. Dynasol Eyewear is a sunglasses distributor available for bulk order sunglasses and wholesale. Visit DynasolEyewear.com to browse our selection and place an order today.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/welcome-to-the-dynasol-eyewear-blog</id>
    <published>2017-01-06T12:59:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-05T12:35:53-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/blogs/posts/welcome-to-the-dynasol-eyewear-blog"/>
    <title>Welcome to the Dynasol Eyewear Blog</title>
    <author>
      <name>Dynasol Eyewear</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p style="float: right;"><img alt="wholesale sunglasses" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1175/0778/files/dynasolemaillogo_medium.jpg?v=1484768674" style="float: right;">Welcome to the Dynasol Eyewear Blog. Dynasol Eyewear’s primary goal is to sell high-quality, fashionable, trendy, and affordable wholesale sunglasses to the masses. We want as many people as possible to own and enjoy a pair of our fashionable sunglasses. With a great selection of sunglasses that is always growing, you are bound to find multiple pairs that appeal to your style and personality.<br><br>Our selection of <a href="https://dynasoleyewear.com/collections/wholesale-sunglasses-deals">wholesale sunglasses</a> is unmatched by the competition. The quality of our wholesale fashion sunglasses surpasses anything our competition can offer. With high-quality bulk order sunglasses in both classic and current styles, you are sure to find the perfect pair to fit your needs. Our frames are available in plastic, metal and bamboo, and in a variety of colors and shapes. We carry polarized sunglasses, aviator, classic, cat eye styles and much more. You are sure to stay on trend and look great with Dynasol Eyewear’s fashion sunglasses.</p>
<p>Other sunglasses wholesalers limit their products to only adult men and women. In addition to having great shades for adults, Dynasol Eyewear carries a great selection of sunglasses for kids. We also have a wide selection of readers for both kids and adults. If you are interested in purchasing high-quality, fashionable bulk order sunglasses or readers, Dynasol Eyewear has the selection that you need.  Visit DynasolEyewear.com and place an order today.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
